ILGWU Legal Department Records 5780/063
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Legal Department Records
1920-1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU)
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Legal Dept.
5780/063
14 cubic feet
14 linear ft.
Legal files, records (documents).
This collection contains correspondence, memoranda, financial reports, and printed material relating to the establishment of the ILGWU's cooperative housing in New York City, as well as research into similar projects elsewhere. Also included in this collection are files on the Ladies' Garment Workers' Center in New York City, arbitration regarding faulty design and construction of Unity House in the Pocono Mountains, Pennsylvania, and contract negotiations in 1979.
8908173
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 14, 2008
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 11, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Biographical / Historical
From very early on in its existence, the ILGWU had need for legal counsel, and this was handled in the union's main offices in cooperation with hired attorneys. As the union grew and especially after the passage of the Taft-Hartley Act in 1947, the union found cause to establish a Legal Department. The department provided general legal counsel to the union and its affiliates, worked to develop collective bargaining agreement terms, and represented the ILGWU in litigation and arbitration. After the formation of the Master Agreements Department in 1965, the responsibilities for developing CBA terms shifted to the new department.
Scope and Contents
The Legal Department records do not comprehensively document the ILGWU legal activities, instead focusing on specific cases or series of cases.
Two ILGWU cases are documented in the Legal Department records. The first case involved the Kellwood Corporation, and the second involved the Donnelly Garment Company. The records relating to the Kellwood case (5780/107, 5780/107 AV, 5780/107 P) include court documents, correspondence and memoranda, surveys of strikers, organizing leaflets and newsletters (from both the union and the company), Steve Honeyman's draft accounts of the strike, audio and transcripts of Honeyman's interviews with ILGWU members and staff, newspaper clippings, photographs, and other printed material. The Donnelly Garment Company's case against the ILGWU is documented primarily through transcripts of the case, legal briefs, and related court documents.
Records on series of cases are the most general and extensive of the Legal Department records. They include records on ILGWU cases in the U.S. courts (5780/081), records documenting cases before the National War Labor Board (5780/085), and records relating to a wide variety contract negotiations, arbitration proceedings, and courts cases (5780/063).
Researchers may find complementary material in the other parts of the ILGWU records, such as the papers of the international leadership, especially the papers of ILGWU presidents (Series IV); the records of local unions in instances where these affiliates were involved in litigation or arbitration (Series III); and the collective bargaining agreements (Series VI). Related collections at the Kheel Center include decisions of the Coat and Suit Industry's Impartial Chairman (6036/015) and decisions of the Dress Industry's Impartial Chairman (6036/017).
This collection contains correspondence, memoranda, financial reports, and printed material relating to the establishment of the ILGWU's cooperative housing in New York City, as well as research into similar projects elsewhere. Also included in this collection are files on the Ladies' Garment Workers' Center in New York City, arbitration regarding faulty design and construction of Unity House in the Pocono Mountains, Pennsylvania, and contract negotiations in 1979.
Also, this collection contains documentation of the ILGWU's legal activities relating to the regulation of homework and the reform of immigration law. Also included are correspondence, memoranda, notes, and legal documents (such as depositions, trial transcripts, and briefs) relating to the Kellwood Company's suit against the ILGWU, the ILGWU and Marlene Industries' proceedings before the National Labor Relations Board, Violetta Putterman's case against the Knitgood Workers' Union Local 155, Thomas Rosario et al.'s case against the Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters' Union Local 10, and miscellaneous other cases.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 5780/107: ILGWU Legal Department Records 5780/107 AV: ILGWU Legal Department Audio-Visual Materials 5780/107 P: ILGWU Legal Department Photographs 5780/081: ILGWU Legal Department Records 5780/162: ILGWU Legal Department Donnelly Garment Company v. ILGWU Records
Women's clothing industry--United States.; Women's clothing industry -- New York (State)-- New York.; Labor unions--Clothing workers--United States.; Labor unions -- Clothing workers -- New York (State)-- New York.; Clothing workers--United States.; Clothing workers -- New York (State)-- New York.; Industrial relations--United States.; Industrial relations -- New York (State) -- New York.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Legal Dept.
8908173
- Local 30 Trusteeship, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Chelsea Housing Legal Matters, 1962-1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Judy Bond, 1961-1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Co-op City, 1965-1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Housing Corp. Loan, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Local 23-25 Merger Proceedings, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Rhoda Lee Inc., 1962-1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Puerto Rico Housing, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Investments. Four Freedoms Inc. Auditors' Reports, 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Investments. Four Freedoms Inc., 1961-1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Four Freedoms Inc., 1966 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Ladies' Garment Workers Center, Inc. New York City, 1920-1928 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Minutes of the Meetings of Ladies Garment Workers Center, Inc., 1921-1927 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Local 142. J. Tuvim, 1961-1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Chelsea Housing. Descriptive Matters, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- East River Housing Corp. Descriptive Matters, 1952-1957 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Chelsea Housing. Construction Matters, 1959-1967 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- East River Housing Corp. Construction Matters, 1952-1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- United Housing, 1967-1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Production Copy-Rights. "With These Hands" (Movie), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Movie "With These Hands", 1951-1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- 70th Anniversary ILGWU, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- 75th Anniversary Celebration, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Cloak Joint Board. H. Mendelsund, 1963-1972 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Unity House/ Pike County Hotels [Folder 1 of 4], 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Unity House/ Pike County Hotels [Folder 2 of 4], 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Unity House/ Pike County Hotels [Folder 3 of 4], 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Unity House/ Pike County Hotels [Folder 4 of 4], 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Negotiations. Imports, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Scope and Contents
  Newspaper Article Included
- Negotiation [Folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Negotiations [Folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Homework: Statements for Services, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Homework: Statements for Services, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Homework: Statements for Services, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Homework: Statements for Services, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Homework: Statements for Services, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Homework: Statements for Services, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Homework: ILGWU v. Dole. Case 89-27, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Newspaper Article Photocopy Included
- Homework: ILGWU v. Dole. Case 89-27, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Newspaper Article Photocopies Included
- Homework: ILGWU v. Dole. Case 89-27 [Folder 1 of 3], 1990 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Newspaper Clippings and Copies Included
- Homework: ILGWU v. Dole. Case 89-27 [Folder 2 of 3], 1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Homework: ILGWU v. Dole. Case 89-27 [Folder 3 of 3], 1990 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Homework: ILGWU v. Dole. Case 89-27, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Homework: ILGWU v. McLaughlin [Folder 1 of 3], 1989 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Civil Action Number 89-27
- Homework: ILGWU v. McLaughlin [Folder 2 of 3], 1989 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Homework: ILGWU v. McLaughlin [Folder 3 of 3], 1989 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Homework: Final Rule. Correspondence and Memos, 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Of January 9, 1989
- Homework: French Creek Sheep and Wool Company [Folder 1 of 2], 1990 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Homework: French Creek Sheep and Wool Company [Folder 2 of 2], 1990 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Homework: Leaflets, Clippings and News Releases, 1988-1994 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Homework: Shea & Gardner [Folder1 of 2], 1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Floppy Disk Included
- Homework: Shea & Gardner [Folder 2 of 2], 1993 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Homework: Shea & Gardner [Folder 1 of 2], 1992 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Homework: Shea & Gardner [Folder 2 of 2], 1992 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Homework: Shea & Gardner [Folder 1 of 2], 1991 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Homework: Shea & Gardner [Folder 2 of 2], 1991 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Homework: U.S. Department of Labor. Notes and Submissions, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Homework: U.S. Department of Labor. Appendix to ILGWU Comments, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Notes and Submissions
- Homework: ILGWU v. Donovan. Correspondence and Memos, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Homework: ILGWU v. Donovan. Correspondence and Memos, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Homework: ILGWU v. Donovan. Correspondence and Memos, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Homework: ILGWU v. Donovan. U.S. Court of Appeals, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  82-2133
- Homework: Legal Memos, Department of Labor, Correspondence [Folder 1 of 3], 1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Homework: Legal Memos, Department of Labor, Correspondence [Folder 2 of 3], 1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Homework: Legal Memos, Department of Labor, Correspondence [Folder 3 of 3], 1981 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Homework: ILGWU v. Donovan. Pleadings [Folder 1 of 7], 1983 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Homework: ILGWU v. Donovan. Pleadings [Folder 2 of 7], 1983 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Homework: ILGWU v. Donovan. Pleadings [Folder 3 of 7], 1983 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Homework: ILGWU v. Donovan. Pleadings [Folder 4 of 7], 1983 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Homework: ILGWU v. Donovan. Pleadings [Folder 5 of 7], 1983 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Homework: ILGWU v. Donovan. Pleadings [Folder 6 of 7], 1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Homework: ILGWU v. Donovan. Pleadings [Folder 7 of 7], 1983 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Homework: Correspondence, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Homework: Dallas, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Homework: Employee Leasing, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Polsinello Files
- Homework: Correspondence, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Homework: Women's Apparel Hearings [Folder 1 of 2], 1989 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Homework: Women's Apparel Hearings [Folder 2 of 2], 1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Homework: Women's Apparel. Correspondence. Memos, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Homework: Department of Labor. Women's Apparel, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Labor's Notice for Women's Apparel
- Homework: Women's Apparel, Correspondence, Memos, Press [Folder 1 of 3], 1989 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Homework: Women's Apparel, Correspondence, Memos, Press [Folder 2 of 3], 1989 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Homework: Women's Apparel, Correspondence, Memos, Press [Folder 3 of 3], 1989 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Homework: Women's Apparel, Correspondence, Memos, Press, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Homework: ILGWU v. Dole. Decision File, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Homework: ILGWU v. Donovan. Pleadings [Folder 1 of 4], 1983 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Homework: ILGWU v. Donovan. Pleadings [Folder 2 of 4], 1983 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Homework: ILGWU v. Donovan. Pleadings [Folder 3 of 4], 1983 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Homework: ILGWU v. Donovan. Pleadings [Folder 4 of 4], 1983 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Homework: ILGWU v. Donovan. Briefs, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Homework: ILGWU v. Donovan. Briefs [Folder 1 of 2], 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Homework: ILGWU v. Donovan. Briefs [Folder 2 of 2], 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Immigration: Ad Hoc Coalition National Immigration Reform Strategy Meeting, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Immigration: ABA Coordinating Committee on Immigration Law [Folder 1 of 2], 1989 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Homework: ABA Coordinating Committee on Immigration Law [Folder 2 of 2], 1989 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Immigration: ABA Coordinating Committee on Immigration Law [Folder 1 of 3], 1988 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Immigration: ABA Coordinating Committee on Immigration Law [Folder 2 of 3], 1988 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Immigration: ABA Coordinating Committee on Immigration Law [Folder 3 of 3], 1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Immigration: ABA Coordinating Committee on Immigration Law [Folder 1 of 2], 1987 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Immigration: ABA Coordinating Committee on Immigration Law [Folder 2 of 2], 1987 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Immigration: ABA Labor Section Committee on Immigration [Folder 1 of 5], 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Immigration: ABA Labor Section Committee on Immigration [Folder 2 of 5], 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Immigration: ABA Labor Section Committee on Immigration [Folder 3 of 5], 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Immigration: ABA Labor Section Committee on Immigration [Folder 4 of 5], 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Immigration: ABA Labor Section Committee on Immigration [Folder 5 of 5], 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Immigration: East Williamsburg Valley Industrial Development Corporation, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  Several Pamphlets Included
- Immigration: Training Materials [Folder 1 of 2], 1985-1988 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Immigration: Training Materials [Folder 2 of 2], 1985-1988 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Papers Regarding Willodean Highbaugh [Folder 1 of 2], 1975-1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Papers Regarding Willodean Highbaugh [Folder 2 of 2], 1975-1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Pending Motion Documents. Volume 1 [Folder 1 of 4], 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Pending Motion Documents. Volume 1 [Folder 2 of 4], 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Pending Motion Documents. Volume 1 [Folder 3 of 4], 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Pending Motion Documents. Volume 1 [Folder 4 of 4], 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Summaries of Depositions [Folder 1 of 2], 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Summaries of Depositions [Folder 2 of 2], 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Neal Rakstang, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  October 3
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Roy Lawrence Fruehauf, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  October 8
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Rick Jenkins, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Depositions of Betty Raymer, John Gillespie and Carolyn Tarter, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  March 18
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Depositions of Loren D. Pruitt, Nelda Vincent and Lois Vincent, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  May 1
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Shirley Culbreth and David Fraim, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  June 4
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Depositions of Zodell Jessie and Anna Lavone Lindsey, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  June 5
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Depositions of Donald Ray Butler and Aedwin Gritton, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  June 17
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Depositions of Peal Webb, Helen Lashley and Patricia Ann Lindsey, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  June 19
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Depositions of Vickie, Judd and Wilma Jaggers, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  June 26
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Depositions of Willa Dean Highbaugh, Venetta Webb, Romie Mae Vincent, Larry Skaggs and Bobby Brooks, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  July 15
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Depositions of Betty Ann Skaggs, Elva Sanders, Mildred Gipson, Nicky Meredith and Charles David Lindsey, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  July 16
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Depositions of Sarah Duvall, Geraldine Collard, Virgil Manco, Maybelle Short and Evelyn Mahoney, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  July 17
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Depositions of Carrie Mae Dennison and Maxine Jones, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  July 31
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Clarence Slaughter, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  September 29
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Frederick W. Wenzel, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  March 3
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Sol Chaikin, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  March 30
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Wilbur Daniels, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Sam Janis, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  June 22
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of David Freeland, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  June 23
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Ruby Geron, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  August 18
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Ralph Cline, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  September 24
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Willodean Highbaugh, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  February 8
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Charles Whitehead, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Vincent J. Manna, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  March 31
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Gary Lusher, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  April 21
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Larry Pitcock, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Charles Hargis, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  April 25
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Kent Thrasher, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of James Veluzat, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Ronnie West, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Terry Barnes, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  April 29
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Richard Barton, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of H.D. Borden, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Roy Ragland, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Edward Lee Powell, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  April 30
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Riley Wyatt, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Jere D. Hopson, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  May 2
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Campbell Lockhart, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Morris Osborne, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Jack Patterson, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Joe Webb, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Edwin Ballard, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  May 3
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Ron Howard, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Eddie Railey, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  May 31
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Louis R. Stiles, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Harry Krugman, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  July 28
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Max Zimny, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Wilbur Daniels, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  July 27
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Thornton O. Fisher, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  August 5
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Arlene Leonard, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  August 19
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of David L. Maller, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  September 13
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Milton Spitz, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  October 18
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Sol Chaikin, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  October 19
- Kellwood v. ILGWU. Deposition of Gus Tyler, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Marlene Industries. Legal Documents, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Marlene Industries. Legal Documents, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Marlene Industries. Legal Documents [Joint Appendix, Volume 1], 1982 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Marlene Industries. Legal Documents [Joint Appendix, Volume 2] [Folder 1 of 3], 1982 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Marlene Industries. Legal Documents [Joint Appendix, Volume 2] [Folder 2 of 3], 1982 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Marlene Industries. Legal Documents [Joint Appendix, Volume 2] [Folder 3 of 3], 1982 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Marlene Industries. Legal Documents [Folder 1 of 2], 1981 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Marlene Industries. Legal Documents [Folder 2 of 2] Marlene Industries. Legal Documents [Folder 2 of 2], 1981 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Marlene Industries. Legal Documents, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Marlene Industries. Legal Documents [Folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Marlene Industries. Legal Documents [Folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Marlene Industries. Legal Documents, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Marlene Industries. Legal Documents, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Marlene Industries. Legal Documents [Folder 1 of 3], 1977 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Marlene Industries. Legal Documents [Folder 2 of 3], 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Marlene Industries. Legal Documents [Folder 3 of 3], 1977 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Marlene Industries. Legal Documents [Folder 1 of 2], 1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Marlene Industries. Legal Documents [Folder 2 of 2], 1976 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Marlene Industries. Legal Documents, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Marlene Industries. Official Report on Proceedings Before the NLRB, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  August 15
- Marlene Industries. Official Report of Proceedings Before the NLRB, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  August 16
- Marlene Industries. Official Report of Proceedings Before the NLRB, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  August 22
- Marlene Industries. Official Report of Proceedings Before the NLRB, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  August 17
- Marlene Industries. Official Report of Proceedings Before the NLRB, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  August 23
- Marlene Industries. Official Report of Proceedings Before the NLRB, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  September 18
- Marlene Industries. Official Report of Proceedings Before the NLRB, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  September 19
- Marlene Industries. Official Report of Proceedings Before the NLRB, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  September 20
- Marlene Industries. Official Report of Proceedings Before the NLRB, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  November 13